firstbanks.com 2003-06-07

# FIRSTBANKS.COM - Privacy Policy

A Commitment to Protect   
Your Customer Information 

**At First Banks, Inc., its subsidiary banks and family of financial companies affiliated through common ownership, we recognize that you have placed your trust in us ... and that preserving your trust is one of the core values of our institution.** This is the reason we are committed to the responsible use and protection of your customer information.

**Here is a summary of our privacy guidelines:**

  * We will maintain the confidentiality of our customers' personal information.
  * We will hold our employees to the highest standards of conduct in ensuring this confidentiality.
  * We will use information responsibly to provide our customers with benefits, improved products and services.
  * We will comply with federal and state privacy laws and regulations.
  * We will establish procedures to maintain accurate information and respond in a timely manner to our customers' request to update or correct information.
  * We will use a combination of safeguards to protect our customers' information against unauthorized access.
  * We will require the companies with which we do business to abide by our privacy policy and to maintain the confidentiality of customer information.

Please read through this brochure to learn more about our privacy policy and how we use and protect your customer information.   

We use customer information in the ordinary course of serving your relationship or managing our business. For example, we use your information to:

  * Identify you and protect you from fraud, so that others cannot use your accounts without authorization.
  * Process your requests, such as purchases, ATM/Debit Card withdrawals or loan applications.
  * Inform you of additional financial services to meet your individual needs. 
  * Service your accounts, issue your account statements, checks and ATM/Debit Cards.

In the process of serving your financial needs, we collect a limited amount of "nonpublic personal information" which can include information about your finances and customer relationship. This customer information helps us better serve your accounts and understand your needs, and may come from a variety of sources, including:    

  * Information we receive directly from you, on applications and other forms, such as your name, address, income and assets. 
  * Information we receive through your transactions or experiences with us or others in the First Banks, Inc. family of financial organizations, such as your account balance, overdraft history, parties to transactions or credit card usage. 
  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies and others as we set up your customer relationship, including credit reports, property appraisals, or verification of employment. 

If you are an Internet user, we may use the information collected about you to provide you with information that may be of interest to you. When accessing our website at www.firstbanks.com, this Privacy Policy is available for you to read there also.  

We strictly limit the sharing of nonpublic personal information both within and outside of the First Banks, Inc. family of financial organizations as follows:

Our affiliates are the subsidiary banks and financial companies listed in this brochure, and are part of the First Banks, Inc. family, being related or affiliated by common ownership or affiliated by common corporate control. Our affiliates share a limited amount of nonpublic personal information internally so that we can serve you more efficiently; offer you new services, such as mortgages, insurance and investments; and reduce the amount of information you are required to provide when you contact us. 

We are permitted by law to share with our affiliates information about your transactions or experiences with us. We do not share other information restricted by law with our affiliates unless we have received your written authorization to do so.

We share nonpublic personal information with nonaffiliated third parties who provide support services for us, such as contract programming or check printing services, as well as selected financial services companies who operate under joint marketing agreements with us. 

This enables us to provide quality service to you and offer you additional financial services that may be of value to you. These arrangements are subject to strict standards of confidentiality and security and are subject to federal and state law. The information we provide is limited to that which we reasonably believe they "need to know" to provide their contracted services.   
In addition, we may disclose nonpublic personal information to third parties as permitted by law. For example, we might be required to disclose information about you in response to a subpoena or under certain federal or state laws or credit bureaus. Or we may provide information to others with your consent, for example to complete a transaction that you have initiated.  
We do not disclose nonpublic personal information to anyone else except as described above.

We have implemented procedures and guidelines to safeguard the privacy of nonpublic personal information from unauthorized use or improper access. We will continue to enhance our security procedures, as new technologies become available. Our employees are governed by a code of conduct and are educated about our privacy policies, and about the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of customer information.

  * If medical information is collected in the course of providing insurance services to you, this information will not be used for any purpose except as you have authorized.
  * We strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. If you believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information, please notify us. We will investigate and correct any inaccuracies. 
  * Our policies for protecting nonpublic personal information apply to customers with a current or former relationship for personal, family or household purposes.

**Rest assured we will keep your information confidential.** We will protect your privacy automatically, every day, without requiring any action on your part. We want you to know that you can trust us - not only to keep your information confidential, but also to provide you with the financial advice and services you need today and in the years to come. Thank you for the opportunity to serve your financial needs.   
This policy is provided to you in accordance with the privacy provisions in Title V of the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act. We may change this policy from time to time, and we will provide an annual notice of our policy to customers with an ongoing relationship. 

The following is a list of First Banks, Inc.'s subsidiary banks and family of financial companies affiliated through common ownership as of March 1, 2002:

First Bank

First Bank & Trust 

First Banks America, Inc.

FB Commercial Finance, Inc.

Missouri Valley Partners, Inc. 

First Securities America, Inc.   
D/B/A First Banc Insurors Agency

First Associate Title, Inc.  
D/B/A First Associate Title

First Title Guaranty  
D/B/A First Banc Insurors Agency

First Brokerage America L.L.C.

First Services, L.P.

First Banc Mortgage, Inc.

First Banc Mortgage, Inc.  
D/B/A First Banc Home Mortgage, Inc. 

First Banc Mortgage, Inc.  
D/B/A FirstBanc Home Mortgage, Inc. 

First Banc Mortgage, Inc.  
D/B/A FB Mortgage, Inc.

First Banc Mortgage, Inc.   
D/B/A FBH Mortgage, Inc.
